

Denys Rokhmaniuk Master of Science in Civil Engineering

Profile

I am a Master of Science in Civil Engineering. I finished 1st and 2nd degree studies at the National University of Water and Natural Resources Management in Rivne. Then I graduated from the second degree studies at the Warsaw University of Life Sciences in Warsaw, specializing in Building Structures.

Work experience

Warehouse worker, Amazon, Wrocław Poland

2020 - 2021

Responsibilities:

- Distributing goods on warehouse shelves,
- Loading and unloading of shipments,
- Completing, packing and preparing goods for shipment,
- Handheld scanner support.

Ventilation fitter, Grunfos, Rivne town

2019-2020

Responsibilities:

- Performing assembly and disassembly of installations and devices ventilation and air conditioning,
 - Control, operation and maintenance of installations and devices ventilation and air conditioning,

• Performing auxiliary construction works related to profession.

Education

Warsaw University of Life Sciences 2020 - 2022

Second-cycle studies in the field of Construction, specializing in Building Structures.

Thesis topic: An entertainment hotel complex project.

National University of Water Economy and Management Natural resources in the town of Rivne 2019 - 2021

Second-cycle studies in the field of Construction, specializing in construction civil industrial and engineering structures.

National University of Water Economy and Management Natural resources in the town of Rivne

2017 - 2019

First-cycle studies in the field of Construction, specializing in construction civil industrial and engineering structures.

A professionally technical college in Rivne

2013 - 2017

Operation of machinery and equipment in the chemical, petroleum and other industries gas. Professional qualification of technicians for service and repair devices.

Languages

Ukraine – native

Polish- upper-Intermediate

English – elementary

Computer skils

MS Ofice, Autocad, Windows, HTML(studying) CSS(studying)

Personal Skills

- Good communication skills
- Analitycal skils
- Desire to learn
- Problem solving at work
- Elasticity in work